const IAS = [
  {
    question: "It is the statement of responsible decision makers about the protection mechanism of a company’s crucial, physical, and information assets?",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Security Policy", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Awareness"],
    answer: "Security Policy"
  },
  {
    question: "Security policy development is a joint or collective operation of all entity of an organization that is affected by its rules.",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Policy Makers", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Audience"],
    answer: "Policy Makers"
  },
  {
    question: "Policy Makers entities that  must render their advice to some form of a review of policies in response to the exceptional or abominable running condition of the business.",
    options: ["Board", "Legal Team", "IT Team", "HR Team"],
    answer: "Board"
  },
  {
    question: "Policy Makers entities usually are the biggest consumers of the policy information in any company because they develop standards around the usage of the computer system, especially security controls.",
    options: ["Board", "Legal Team", "IT Team", "HR Team"],
    answer: "IT Team"
  },
  {
    question: "Policy Makers entities that ensures the legal points in the document and guides a particular point of  appropriateness in the company. ",
    options: ["Board", "Legal Team", "HR Team", "IT Team"],
    answer: "Legal Team"
  },
  {
    question: "Policy Makers entities typically obtains a certified certificate from each employee, in which they have read and understood the stipulated policy, as it deals with reward- and punishment-related issues of employees to implement discipline",
    options: ["Board", "Legal Team", "HR Team", "IT Team"],
    answer: "HR Team"
  },
  {
    question: "Security policy applies to all senior management, employees, stockholders, consultants, and service providers who use company assets.",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Policy Makers", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Audience"],
    answer: "Policy Audience"
  },
  {
    question: "It guides its audience what to do according to the stipulated terms and conditions of a company.",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Policy Makers", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Audience"],
    answer: "Policy Classification"
  },
  {
    question: "It mandates what protection should be wielded to safeguard the physical asset from both employees and management and applies to the prevail facilities, including doors, entry point, surveillance, and alarm.",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Hardware and Software", "Physical Security", "Personnel Management"],
    answer: "Physical Security"
  },
  {
    question: "– They are supposed to tell their employees how to conduct or operate day-to-day business activities in a secure manner. For instance, password management and confidential information security apply to individual employees.",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Hardware and Software", "Physical Security", "Personnel Management"],
    answer: "Personnel Management"
  },
  {
    question: "It directs the administrator what type of technology to use and how network control should be configured and applied to the system and network administrators.",
    options: ["Policy Classification", "Hardware and Software", "Physical Security", "Personnel Management"],
    answer: "Hardware and Software"
  },
  {
    question: "Security documents are living documents. It needs to be updated at specific intervals in response to changing business and customer requirements.",
    options: ["Policy Audit", "Security Policy", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Awareness"],
    answer: "Policy Audit"
  },
  {
    question: " A successful security audit accomplishes the following except one",
    options: ["It compares the security policy with the actual practice in place", 
  "It determines the exposure to threats from the inside", 
  "Finalizes the policy without further study and does not have gather enough information", 
  "It also determines the exposure of an organization from an outside attack."],
    answer: "Finalizes the policy without further study and does not have gather enough information"
  },
  {
    question: "Administration of security policies ensures compliance with the principle and practices dictated by the company because policy procedure does not work if they are violated.",
    options: ["Policy Audit", "Security Policy", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Awareness"],
    answer: "Policy Enforcement"
  },
  {
    question: "Company employees are often perceived as a “soft” target to be compromised because they are the least predictable and easiest to exploit.",
    options: ["Policy Audit", "Security Policy", "Policy Enforcement", "Policy Awareness"],
    answer: "Policy Awareness"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data that seeks to protect the most sensitive data. Within a large organization, which has requirements to keep customer or client data secure, there is often a limited number of people who have access to the data.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "Privileged Password Management", "Firewall Audit Checklist", "Network Administration Daily Tasks"],
    answer: "Privileged Password Management"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data using checklist aims to list a series of key daily tasks performed by network administrators and provide space for those tasks to be recorded.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "Privileged Password Management", "Firewall Audit Checklist", "Network Administrator Daily Tasks"],
    answer: "Network Administrator Daily Tasks"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data that deals with hardware and software, training, and procedures.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "Network Security Audit Checklist", "Firewall Audit Checklist", "Network Administrator Daily Tasks"],
    answer: "Network Security Audit Checklist"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data that is thorough and covers a series of precautions.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "Network Security Audit Checklist", "Firewall Audit Checklist", "Virtual Private Network (VPN) Configuration"],
    answer: "Firewall Audit Checklist"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data that allows the staff member to connect to the office network remotely.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "Network Security Audit Checklist", "Firewall Audit Checklist", "Virtual Private Network (VPN) Configuration"],
    answer: "Virtual Private Network (VPN) Configuration"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data fighting off phishing attacks and other malicious attempts to compromise security relies on both strong technical resilience and a high level of professional training",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "E-mail Server Security", "Penetration Testing", "Virtual Private Network (VPN) Configuration"],
    answer: "E-mail Server Security"
  },
  {
    question: "Security process to protect and manage data involves testing systems security by trying to break into it, it is centered around trying to find vulnerabilities in a system and then attempting to sneak inside.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "E-mail Server Security", "Penetration Testing", "Virtual Private Network (VPN) Configuration"],
    answer: "Penetration Testing"
  },
  {
    question: "Enables the identification and correction of trends that could lead to business problems such as network instability and service interruption.",
    options: ["Apache Server Security", "Network Compliance", "Penetration Testing", "Virtual Private Network (VPN) Configuration"],
    answer: "Network Compliance"
  },
  {
    question: "Is the science of secret writing to keep the data secret and an important aspect when dealing with network security.",
    options: ["Cryptanalysis", "Network Compliance", "Penetration Testing", "Cryptography"],
    answer: "Cryptography"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of Cryptography that involves usage of one (1) secret key along with encryption and decryption algorithms which help in securing the contents of the message.",
    options: ["Asymmetric key criptography", "Symmetric key criptography", "Hashing", "Cryptography"],
    answer: "Symmetric key criptography"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of Cryptography that also known as “public key cryptography,” it involves the usage of a public key along with the secret key.",
    options: ["Asymmetric key criptography", "Symmetric key criptography", "Hashing", "Cryptography"],
    answer: "Asymmetric key criptography"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of Cryptography that involves taking the plain-text and converting it to a hash value of fixed size by a hash function.",
    options: ["Asymmetric key criptography", "Symmetric key criptography", "Hashing", "Cryptography"],
    answer: "Hashing"
  },
  {
    question: "Is the study of cipher text, ciphers, and cryptosystems to understand how they work as well as find and improve techniques for defeating or weakening threats.",
    options: ["Cryptanalysis", "Network Compliance", "Penetration Testing", "Cryptography"],
    answer: "Cryptanalysis"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of attacks in Criptanalysis that can be divided into mathematical analysis and brute force attacks.",
    options: ["Implementation Attacks", "Phising", "Classical Attack", "Social Engineering Attack"],
    answer: "Classical Attack"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of attacks in Criptanalysis that can trick someone into revealing their passwords to the attacker or allowing access to the restricted area comes under this attack.",
    options: ["Implementation Attacks", "Phising", "Classical Attack", "Social Engineering Attack"],
    answer: "Social Engineering Attack"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of attacks in Criptanalysis is a side-channel analysis can be used to obtain a secret key for this kind of attack.",
    options: ["Implementation Attacks", "Phising", "Classical Attack", "Social Engineering Attack"],
    answer: "Implementation Attacks"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of Classical Attack that run the encryption algorithm for all possible cases of the keys until these find a match.",
    options: ["Brute Force Attack", "Analytical Attacks", "Classical Attack", "Social Engineering Attack"],
    answer: "Brute Force Attack"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of Classical Attack that those attacks which focus on breaking the cryptosystem by analyzing the internal structure of the encryption algorithm",
    options: ["Brute Force Attack", "Analytical Attacks", "Classical Attack", "Social Engineering Attack"],
    answer: "Analytical Attacks"
  },
  {
    question: "Network compliance and security is imperative for ensuring quality service, meeting implementation and regulatory requirements, and managing risks.",
    options: ["True", "False", "Trulse", "Frue"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "It is one of the earliest known and simpliest.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Ceasar Cipher", "Keyword Ciphers"],
    answer: "Ceasar Cipher"
  },
  {
    question: "To use this method for constructing the ciphertext alphabet, pick a keyword and write it down while ignoring the repeated letters follow it with the letters of the alphabet that have not yet been used.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Ceasar Cipher", "Keyword Ciphers"],
    answer: "Keyword Ciphers"
  },
  {
    question: "It is a type of substitution cipher in which each letter in the plaintext is shifted to a certain number of places down the alphabet.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Caesar Cipher", "Keyword Ciphers"],
    answer: "Caesar Cipher"
  },
  {
    question: "Similar to Keyword Ciphers but can pick a keyletter and begin the keyword UNDER that letter of the plaintext.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Caesar Cipher", "Polyalphabetic Ciphers"],
    answer: "Giovanni's Method"
  },
  {
    question: "It is archived by performing some permutation on the plaintext letters, simplest such cipher is the rail fence technique, in which the plaintext is written down as a sequence of diagonals and then read off as a sequence of rows.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Polyalphabetic Ciphers", "Keyword Ciphers"],
    answer: "Transposition Techniques"
  },
  {
    question: "Another way to improve on the simple monoalphabetic techniques is to use different monoalphabetic substitutions as on proceeds through the plaintext message.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Polyalphabetic Ciphers", "Keyword Ciphers"],
    answer: "Polyalphabetic Ciphers"
  },
  {
    question: "The best-known and the simplest algorithm is referred to as the Vigenere cipher.",
    options: ["Giovanni's Method", "Transposition Techniques", "Polyalphabetic Ciphers", "Keyword Ciphers"],
    answer: "Polyalphabetic Ciphers"
  },
  {
    question: "Caesar Cipher is named after (inventor) who used to communicate with his generals",
    options: ["Jake Caesar", "John Caesar", "Julius Caesar", "Justin Caesar"],
    answer: "Julius Caesar"
  },
  {
    question: "He suggested that one can also pick a keyletter and begin the keyword UNDER that letter of the plaintext.",
    options: ["Giovanni Battista Argenti", "Giovanni Battista Argentina", "Giovanni Bautista Argenti", "Giovanni Bautista Argentina Sardines"],
    answer: "Giovanni Battista Argenti"
  },
  {
    question: "Polyalphabetic Ciphers algorithm reffered to as the _______?",
    options: ["Venise Cipher", "Vigenere Cipher", "Vigenre Cipher", "Willie Revillame"],
    answer: "Vigenere Cipher"
  },
   {
    question: "Refers to any group of users, workstations, devices, printers, computers, and database servers that share different types of data via network resources.",
    options: ["Domain", "Browser", "Server", "Application"],
    answer: "Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "This covers all the users that have access to the other domains.",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "Workstation Domain", "WAN Domain", "User Domain"],
    answer: "User Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "It is a computer of an individual user where the production takes place.",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "Workstation Domain", "WAN Domain", "User Domain"],
    answer: "Workstation Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "This contains all of the workstation, hubs, switches, and routers. This isalso a trusted zone.",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "Workstation Domain", "WAN Domain", "LAN/WAN Domain"],
    answer: "LAN Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "It consists of the Internet and semi-private lines.",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "WAN Domain", "Remote Access Domain", "LAN/WAN Domain"],
    answer: "WAN Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "It is the boundary between the trusted and untrusted zones. The zones are filtered with a firewall.",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "WAN Domain", "Remote Access Domain", "LAN/WAN Domain"],
    answer: "LAN/WAN Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "This domain is made up of user-accessed servers such as e-mail and database",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "System/Application Domain", "Remote Access Domain", "LAN/WAN Domain"],
    answer: "System/Application Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "This is the domain in which a mobile user can access the local network usually through a VPN",
    options: ["LAN Domain", "System/Application Domain", "Remote Access Domain", "LAN/WAN Domain"],
    answer: "Remote Access Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in User Domain except one",
    options: ["User can use the password to delete his/her file", 
	      "A fire can destroy primary data", 
	      "User can destroy data in the application (intentionally or not) and delete all", 
	      "User can insert infected CD or flash drive into the computer"],
    answer: "A fire can destroy primary data"
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in Workstation Domain except one",
    options: ["A workstation’s hard drive can fail to cause loss of data.", 
	      "The workstation’s operating system can have a known software vulnerability that allows a hacker to connect remotely and steal data.", 
	      "User can destroy data in the application (intentionally or not) and delete all", 
	      "A workstation’s browser can have a software vulnerability,which allows unsigned scripts to install malicious software silently."],
    answer: "User can destroy data in the application (intentionally or not) and delete all"
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in LAN Domain except one",
    options: ["A work can spread through the LAN and infect all computers in it.", 
	      "LAN server OS can have a known software vulnerability.", 
	      "An unauthorized user can access the organization’s workstations in a LAN.", 
	      "A firewall with unnecessary ports open can allow access from the Internet."],
    answer: "A firewall with unnecessary ports open can allow access from the Internet."
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in WAN Domain except one",
    options: ["Server can receive a Denial of Service (DOS) or Distributed Denial of Service (DDOS) attack.", 
	      "A file transfer protocol (FTP) can allow anonymously uploaded illegal software", 
	      "An unauthorized user can access the organization’s workstations in a WAN.", 
	      "The service provider can have a major network outage."],
    answer: "An unauthorized user can access the organization’s workstations in a WAN."
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in LAN/WAN Domain except one",
    options: ["Remote communication from the office can be unsecured.", 
	      "A firewall with unnecessary ports open can allow access from the Internet", 
	      "A hacker can penetrate an IT infrastructure and gain access to the internal network."],
    answer: "Remote communication from the office can be unsecured."
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in Remote Access Domain except one",
    options: ["Remote communication from the office can be unsecured.", 
	      "A firewall with unnecessary ports open can allow access from the Internet", 
	      "Communication circuit outage can deny connection."],
    answer: "A firewall with unnecessary ports open can allow access from the Internet"
  },
 {
    question: "Following are the risks in System/Application Domain except one",
    options: ["The service provider can have a major network outage.", 
	      "A DOS attack can cripple the organization’s e-mail.", 
	      "A fire can destroy primary data", 
	      "A database server can be attacked by SQL injection, corrupting the data."],
    answer: "The service provider can have a major network outage."
  },
 {
    question: "Those whose username and encrypted password are stored in the computer itself.",
    options: ["Domain Users", 
	      "Drug Users", 
	      "Local Users", 
	      "Remote Users"],
    answer: "Local Users"
  },
 {
    question: "Those whose username and password are stored on a domain controller rather than the computer and the user is logging into.",
    options: ["Domain Users", 
	      "Drug Users", 
	      "Local Users", 
	      "Remote Users"],
    answer: "Domain Users"
  },
 {
    question: "This domain is defined as a sub-network that is made up of servers and clients—each of which is controlled by a centralized database. ",
    options: ["MAN Domain", 
	      "LAN Domain", 
	      "WAN Domain", 
	      "Remote Domain"],
    answer: "LAN Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "A communications network that spans a large geographic area such as cities, states, or countries. It can be private to connect parts of a business, or it can be more public to connect smaller networks.",
    options: ["MAN Domain", 
	      "LAN Domain", 
	      "WAN Domain", 
	      "Remote Domain"],
    answer: "WAN Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "Enables remote users to access files and other system resources on any devices or servers that are connected to the network at any time, increasing employee productivity and enabling them to better collaborate with colleagues around the world.",
    options: ["MAN Domain", 
	      "LAN Domain", 
	      "WAN Domain", 
	      "Remote Access Domain"],
    answer: "Remote Access Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "What is IP security VPN (IPsec VPN)?",
    options: ["A piece of software called “VPN client” is installed in the end user’s computer and is configured with details about the target network, such as the gateway IP address and a preshared security key",
	      "Common encryption technology that is widely used to provide secure communication on the Internet.",
	      "A relatively new player to the remote access arena that was not developed by a firewall manufacturer, but rather by Microsoft."
	     ],
    answer: "A piece of software called “VPN client” is installed in the end user’s computer and is configured with details about the target network, such as the gateway IP address and a preshared security key"
  },
 {
    question: "What is Secure Socket Layer VPN (SSL VPN)?",
    options: ["A piece of software called “VPN client” is installed in the end user’s computer and is configured with details about the target network, such as the gateway IP address and a preshared security key",
	      "A relatively new player to the remote access arena that was not developed by a firewall manufacturer, but rather by Microsoft.",
	      "Common encryption technology that is widely used to provide secure communication on the Internet."
	      ],
    answer: "Common encryption technology that is widely used to provide secure communication on the Internet."
  },
 {
    question: "What is Microsoft Direct Access?",
    options: ["A piece of software called “VPN client” is installed in the end user’s computer and is configured with details about the target network, such as the gateway IP address and a preshared security key",
	      "A relatively new player to the remote access arena that was not developed by a firewall manufacturer, but rather by Microsoft.",
	      "Common encryption technology that is widely used to provide secure communication on the Internet."
	      ],
    answer: "A relatively new player to the remote access arena that was not developed by a firewall manufacturer, but rather by Microsoft."
  },
 {
    question: "This consists of all of a business’ mission-critical systems, applications, and data. It is important to ensure that this domain is secure at all times.",
    options: ["MAN Domain", 
	      "LAN Domain", 
	      "System/Application Domain", 
	      "Remote Access Domain"
	     ],
    answer: "System/Application Domain"
  },
 {
    question: "This can be defined as (gaining access to a physical entity or area without permission from an administrative figure).",
    options: ["Unauthorized Logical Access", 
	      "Unauthorized Physical Access", 
	      "Server Vulnerabilities", 
	      "Software Vulnerabilities"
	     ],
    answer: "Unauthorized Physical Access"
  },
 {
    question: "This is nearly identical to unauthorized physical access, except it is not limited to tangible data.",
    options: ["Unauthorized Logical Access", 
	      "Unauthorized Physical Access", 
	      "Server Vulnerabilities", 
	      "Software Vulnerabilities"
	     ],
    answer: "Unauthorized Logical Access"
  },
 {
    question: "This is a flaw that exists in the programming of a software component or system that allows a malicious attacker to gain unauthorized access to that system through an exploit.",
    options: ["Unauthorized Logical Access", 
	      "Unauthorized Physical Access", 
	      "Server Vulnerabilities", 
	      "Software Vulnerabilities"
	     ],
    answer: "Software Vulnerabilities"
  },
 {
    question: "Non-server systems with the exception that software vulnerabilities that can exist on servers have the potential to be even more damaging.",
    options: ["Software Vulnerabilities",
	      "Unauthorized Logical Access", 
	      "Unauthorized Physical Access", 
	      "Server Vulnerabilities"
	     ],
    answer: "Server Vulnerabilities"
  },
 {
    question: "Occurs when any stored data is destroyed.",
    options: ["Cyber Attack",
	      "Unauthorized Logical Access", 
	      "Data Loss", 
	      "Server Vulnerabilities"
	     ],
    answer: "Data Loss"
  },
 {
    question: "Refers to the code of responsible behavior on the Internet. The basic rule is (Do not do something in cyberspace that you would consider wrong or illegal in everyday life).",
    options: ["Cyber Attack",
	      "Cyber Ethics", 
	      "Data Loss", 
	      "Cybersecurity"
	     ],
    answer: "Cyber Ethics"
  },
 {
    question: "Offers a framework for what he calls a global “ethics in technology” manifesto",
    options: ["Cybersecurity Manifesto",
	      "Ethical Manifesto", 
	      "Ethics Manifesto", 
	      "Theoritical Manifesto"
	     ],
    answer: "Ethics Manifesto"
  },
 {
    question: "Author of Ethics Manifesto",
    options: ["Kawhi Leonard",
	      "Gerd Leonhard", 
	      "Gerald Leonhard", 
	      "Vic Sotto"
	     ],
    answer: "Gerd Leonhard"
  },
 {
    question: "We can be employed, use public services, buy things, and function in society without a requirement to deploy the technology on or inside our bodies.",
    options: ["The right to disconnect",
	      "The right to remain natural", 
	      "The right to be anonymous", 
	      "The right to employ or involve people instead of machines"
	     ],
    answer: "The right to remain natural"
  },
 {
    question: "We must be able to choose to be slower than technology and not make efficiency more important than humanity.",
    options: ["The right to disconnect",
	      "The right to remain natural", 
	      "The right to be inefficient if and where it defines our basic humanities", 
	      "The right to employ or involve people instead of machines"
	     ],
    answer: "The right to be inefficient if and where it defines our basic humanities"
  },
 {
    question: "We must retain the right to switch off connectivity, go dark on the network,and pause communication, tracking, and monitoring.",
    options: ["The right to disconnect",
	      "The right to remain natural", 
	      "The right to be inefficient if and where it defines our basic humanities", 
	      "The right to employ or involve people instead of machines"
	     ],
    answer: "The right to disconnect"
  },
 {
    question: "We must retain the option of not being identified and tracked, such as when using a digital application or platform when it doesn’t pose a risk or impose itself on others.",
    options: ["The right to disconnect",
	      "The right to remain natural", 
	      "The right to be anonymous", 
	      "The right to employ or involve people instead of machines"
	     ],
    answer: "The right to be anonymous"
  },
 {
    question: "We should not allow companies or employers to be disadvantaged if they choose to use people instead of machines even if it’s more expensive and less efficient.",
    options: ["The right to disconnect",
	      "The right to remain natural", 
	      "The right to be anonymous", 
	      "The right to employ or involve people instead of machines"
	     ],
    answer: "The right to employ or involve people instead of machines"
  },
 {
    question: "Following are three core ethic values except one",
    options: ["Objectivity",
	      "Good Boy", 
	      "Integrity", 
	      "Professional Competence and Due Care"
	     ],
    answer: "Good Boy"
  }
];
export default IAS;
